<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anna Bardenhagen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anna Bardenhagen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Python</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/learning-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/learning-python/</guid>
      <description>During the last few weeks of SDS348, we have been learning some of the basics of Python. While my first instinct was to stick to what I know best (R), Python has proven itself to be pretty interesting and versatile, although I will have to put a lot more work into it before I start feeling more comfortable. There are quite a few differences between R and Python, but two of the most basic differences come across when indexing in either program and when you come across a type of dataframe called a dictionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Background For this project, I decided to look at two datasets: the percentage of breastfed infants by state, and the monthly average number of persons participating in Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP) by state. These datasets were from KFF.org, a website by the Kaiser Family Foundation that contains a large amount of health and demographic data by state. The &amp;quot;Breastfed&amp;quot; dataset contains four variables: one for location, which lists the states and territories (excluding Puerto Rico) in the US, and three which represent the proportion of infants in each state that were breastfed at three timepoints: at six months, at twelve months, and at any point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The dataset I chose to analyze is from the UCI Machine Learning Repository, and is called the Contraceptive Method Choice Data Set. It is a subset of the 1987 National Indonesia Contraceptive Prevalence Survey. The variables in this survey are the age, education, religion, and work status of the wife, the education of the husband, the number of children ever born, the standard of living, the level of media exposure the couple has, and the method of contraception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
